<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CityTour</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">I´m here</string>
    <string name="previous">Next stop</string>

    <string name="goTo_brandenburgGate">Go to the \n Brandenburg Gate</string>
    <string name="name_brandenburgGate">Brandenburg Gate</string>
    <string name="info_brandenburgGate">
        Situated in the heart of Berlin, the Brandenburg Gate is an iconic
        symbol of German unity and a monumental testament to the country\'s rich history.
        Constructed between 1788 and 1791, the neoclassical gate was inspired by the entrance to
        the Acropolis in Athens. Commissioned by King Frederick William II of Prussia, it was
        originally designed to represent peace.\n\nThe gate features five passages, with the
        central one previously reserved for royalty. Atop the structure sits the Quadriga, a
        chariot drawn by four horses and driven by the goddess of victory, which has seen its own
        share of history, being taken by Napoleon to Paris in the early 19th century before being
        returned to Berlin.\n\nOver the centuries, the Brandenburg Gate has witnessed numerous
        significant events, from military parades to Cold War tensions. It was just in front of
        the gate that the notorious Berlin Wall severed the city in two from 1961 to 1989. The gate,
        thus, became a poignant symbol of division during those years. The fall of the Wall in 1989
        saw jubilant celebrations at the Brandenburg Gate, solidifying its status as an emblem of
        unity and freedom.\n\nToday, the Brandenburg Gate stands not only as an architectural
        masterpiece but also as a beacon of hope, resilience, and the enduring spirit of the German
        people. A visit to Berlin is incomplete without witnessing this historic landmark, which
        serves as a reminder of both the turbulent past and the hopeful future of the nation.
    </string>

    <string name="name_eastSideGallery">East Side Gallery</string>
    <string name="info_eastSideGallery">
        The East Side Gallery in Berlin stands as a vibrant testament to freedom and is one of the
        city\'s most visited landmarks. Situated along a 1.3 km stretch of the remnants of the Berlin
        Wall, it is the longest-standing segment of the Wall left today. Immediately after the
        Wall\'s fall in 1989, artists from around the world flocked to Berlin to transform this
        symbol of division and repression into a work of art. Today, the Gallery showcases over
        100 murals, reflecting the joy and hope for a world without walls.\n\n
        The paintings on the Wall address themes of peace, freedom, and the broader implications of
        a world united. Some of the most iconic images, like Dmitri Vrubel's "My God, Help Me to
        Survive This Deadly Love" depicting the brotherly kiss between Leonid Brezhnev and Erich
        Honecker, have become emblematic of the spirit of the time.\n\n
        Easily accessible and free to the public, the East Side Gallery not only provides a visual
        history lesson but also serves as a symbol of hope, demonstrating the transformative power
        of art. Visitors walking along this open-air gallery will be moved by its poignant reminders
        of a city's divided past and its dreams for the future.
    </string>

    <string name="name_tvTower">TV Tower</string>
    <string name="info_tvTower">
        Dominating the skyline of Berlin at a staggering height of 368 meters, the Berlin TV Tower,
        or Fernsehturm, is not only the city\'s tallest structure but also an iconic symbol of its
        historic and contemporary significance. Located near Alexanderplatz in the heart of the
        city, the tower was originally constructed between 1965 and 1969 by the government of the
        German Democratic Republic (East Germany) as a symbol of Communist power and achievement.\n\n
        Beyond its political symbolism, the Fernsehturm offers an unparalleled panoramic view of
        the city from its observation deck. On a clear day, visitors can see for miles in every
        direction, capturing both the modern bustle and historic landmarks of Berlin. The tower also
        boasts a revolving restaurant, allowing guests to enjoy a full 360-degree view as they dine.\n\n
        Its unique "pop art" sphere design, coupled with its historical context, makes the Berlin
        TV Tower an essential stop for any visitor looking to grasp the breadth and depth of
        Berlin's urban landscape and its storied past. Whether you're marveling at it from a
        distance or gazing out from its summit, the Fernsehturm stands as a captivating beacon of
        Berlin's multifaceted identity.
    </string>


    <string name="name_holocaust">Holocaust Memorial</string>
    <string name="info_holocaust">
        Situated in the heart of Berlin, the Holocaust Memorial, officially named the Memorial to
        the Murdered Jews of Europe, is a somber yet poignant tribute to the six million Jews who
        were persecuted and murdered during the Holocaust. Designed by architect Peter Eisenman and
        inaugurated in 2005, the memorial comprises 2,711 concrete slabs, or "stelae", arranged in
        a grid pattern on a sloping field, spanning over 19,000 square meters.\n\n
        Walking amidst the varying heights of the stelae, visitors are engulfed in a disorienting
        and contemplative atmosphere. The design purposefully avoids any specific interpretations,
        allowing individuals to imbue the space with personal reflection and remembrance. The
        memorial's abstract nature serves as an invitation to ponder the immense scale of human
        tragedy it represents.
        Beneath the field of stelae lies an underground information center, where visitors can delve
        deeper into the personal stories of the victims, learn about the broader history of the
        Holocaust, and understand the memorial's significance.\n\n
        The Holocaust Memorial stands as a powerful testament to the atrocities of the past, urging
        visitors to remember, reflect upon, and ensure that such horrors are never repeated. Its
        central location in Berlin underlines the city's commitment to confronting its dark history
        and promoting a message of tolerance and understanding.
    </string>

    <string name="name_parliament">Berlin Parliament</string>
    <string name="info_parliament">
        Perched on the banks of the River Spree, the Reichstag Building, home to Germany\'s
        Bundestag (Federal Parliament), is a melding of historic grandeur and modern architecture.
        Originally opened in 1894, this neo-Renaissance edifice bore witness to many tumultuous
        events of the 20th century, from the burning of the Reichstag in 1933 to the fall of the
        Berlin Wall in 1989.\n\n
        After Germany\'s reunification, the building was extensively renovated under the guidance of
        renowned British architect Sir Norman Foster. His most notable addition is the striking
        glass dome that crowns the structure. This transparent dome, symbolic of Germany's
        commitment to transparency and democracy, offers visitors a 360-degree view of the city,
        while its mirrored core reflects light into the parliamentary chamber below.\n\n
        Inside, guided tours allow visitors to grasp the workings of the German political system
        and the building's historical significance. The Reichstag's storied past, combined with its
        architectural prowess, makes it a must-visit for anyone keen on understanding Berlin's
        intricate history and its enduring dedication to democracy.
    </string>

</resources>